Guide to the Stanford University, Dean of Student Affairs, Office of Student Activities, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Dean of Student Affairs, Office of Student Activities, records
1961-1981
SC0299
Stanford University. Dean of Student Affairs.
Stanford University. Dean of Student Affairs. Office of Student Activities.
10.5 Linear feet
Contains office files of student organizations, administrative files of the office, and files of the Associated Students of Stanford University (ASSU).
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
Contains office files of student organizations, administrative files of the office, and files of the Associated Students of Stanford University (ASSU).
Access Terms
Associated Students of Stanford University.; Stanford University -- General subdivision--Students.;; Stanford University. Associated Students.; Stanford University. Dean of Student Affairs. Office of Student Activities.
Collection Contents
- Records, Accession ARCH-1984-024
  - C.O.P.E. 1972-76 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - C.O.S.S. Subcommittee, Minority Affairs, 1975-76 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - C.O.S.S. 1973-79 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Student Evaluation of Teaching Committee 1970-71 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Evaluation of Teaching minutes 1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Child Care Policy Study 1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Education and Employment of Women 1978-79 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - C.E.E.W.U. 1972-73 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Committee on the Education and Employment of Women in the University, 1972-73 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - C.E.E.W. 1973-76 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Student publications (general) 1977-85 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Off-Campus Student Center 1976-80 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - OCSC Carpool evaluation, questionnaire and budget 1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - OCSC Coordinator – resumes 1976-77 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Off-Campus student questionnaire 1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Survey of off-campus students, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - O.C.S.C. flyers (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - O.C.S.C. informers 1978 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - OCSC correspondence, 1976-78 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Graduate student lounge 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - OCSC 1978 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - OCSC financial business 1975-76 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Comm. On the Physically Limited, 1980-81 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Accessibility surveys, 1980-81 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Committee on Disabled Students 1977 (Box 1, Folder 25)